

# OLEKSANDR KRYVCHENKO

AUTOMATION TESTER
(JavaScript)

### CONTACT

- +34 691 328 818
- @ amzkryvchenko@gmail.com
- live:.cid.7d60ceebf1c9c52c
- in oleksandr-kryvchenko
- github.com/Kryvchenko
- kryvchenko.com

### PRO SKILLS

HTML/CSS

React

Jenkins

Javascript

Node

Git

Webdriver I/O

Cypress

Postman

Jira

Jest



I am a QA automation tester with extensive web development skills. Having almost a decade of customer service experience, dedicated and quality-oriented professional. I find myself easily establishing and maintaining relationships with colleagues which has historically been increasing team unity and productivity.

### **EXPERIENCES**

### **AUTOMATION TESTER**

IN 2022

#### EPAM, MALAGA, SPAIN (MENTORING PROGRAM)

- Developed test automation frameworks from scratch
- Provided results report and debug.
- Conducted test planning, requirements testing.
- Worked with test cases, scenarios, defect reporting.
- Worked Git versioning.
- Conducted API automation testing with Postman.
- Performed CI/CD with Jenkins, pipelines with tests.
- Performed testing, with JS Automation frameworks: WDIO, Cypress.
- Used JS Tools: Mocha, Chai.
- Learned Agile, Scrum, Kanban and other project management tools.
- Tested WebServices.

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

IN 2021 - 2022

#### SKILLUP ACADEMY (APPRENTICESHIP)

- Preferably used modern JavaScript (ES6) library React.js for logic task accomplishment with TypeScript like good practices.
- Coded signed off designs into working web page templates in HTML5, CSS (LESS/SASS preprocessors) and then integrated those into content management systems.
- Used mobile first and pixel perfect technique. CSS Grids for building responsive websites with scalability in mind.
- Used React Redux for centralizing application's state and logic.
- Used Git versioning for coordinating work among programmers.
- Worked with API calls and submitted requests to the server.
- Partnered QA in testing tasks.

#### SALES SPECIALIST

IN 2019 - 2022

HAMILTON PRINCESS, FAIRMONT, HAMILTON, BERMUDA

SALES AND MARKETING SPECIALIST

IN 2016 - 2019

PROMAN MAGAZINE, KYIV, UKRAINE

SALES AND MARKETING SPECIALIST

IN 2014 - 2016

ILAYA INTERNATIONAL GROUP, KYIV, UKRAINE



## EDUCATIONS

#### MASTER - ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING

IN 2012 - 2014

NATIONAL AVIATION UNIVERSITY

- Member of the University Management Club

#### BACHELOR - RADIO ELECTRONIC DEVICES

IN 2007 - 2012

NATIONAL AVIATION UNIVERSITY

- Recipient of full merit based and athletic scholarship
- Member of the University Management Club



### TRAININGS

#### FRONT-END (SKILLUP)

**TEST AUTOMATION JS (EPAM)** 

Javascript, HTML/CSS, React, Git, SCSS, Lodash, MUI, Redux

Mentoring program